For that you're in action,
Beast there a G,
Mission of clue.
Where you seek a throne,
Only one's never out.
Hi, good evening.
Hey man, yeah, thanks for letting me know about that.
Somebody else was showing me that.
She's a nut, Carolyn Mabry.
Oh, is that Jimmy and Chickencakes?
Yeah, she's a liar.
You know, I...
She's just nasty because even Bita knows the truth, all of us did, Jamie, all of them,
because Gia used to complain about her saying she's real creepy and everything and that she
was trying to start going live because after Attila did a panel or whatever,
some of them were trying to go live and she was trying to use Gia and her husband,
you know, he doesn't sleep with her anymore. He's got another woman and he'd be gone out of town or
And so she was begging Gia to come stay at her place and Gia kind of freaked out and she wanted her to stay with her and do lives with her and, you know, and she thought she was going to become famous or something that Gia was creeped out by her and I have the text because, you know, but Gia went back and forth a lot with a lot of people.
But I remember me and those people, Abinda, and the other people we discussed it after
Gia passed, and everybody has the same notes that, yes, it's true that she would complain
about those chicken cakes.
And that's why I called chicken cakes out in Steve's chat when she showed up.
And remember, I don't know if you remember or knew that everybody kicked her out of the
community and she was crying because KK chased her off and started everybody else, because
And she's a cokehead.
And that's why she was nodding out that day when Alex caught her.
And she's lying for attention, and I'll expose all of that, especially Gia's messages about
her and everybody knows, even Jamie.
And I think Chicken Cakes was obsessed with Jamie at one time because she'd be all over
And, you know, she's a cokehead and a druggy.
She was in DX and they got sick of her and she was always wanting money, begging for
money.
And she said that she didn't have food and she has a kid, so they would start sending
her food and she didn't like, she didn't like that.
She said she preferred money instead.
And and they kicked her ass out like they kick her out everywhere even good times and she was crying
You know when he was done with her
So all of a sudden she started hit me up, you know
And and and said I can help you with YouTube and all this stuff and I'm thinking I don't plan on going live
I just do videos
And she was just trying so hard and when she was coked out of her mind and she asked me would you know
She needed money and she
She was offering to sell me Coke and I said no, I had a problem with Coke before and
plus I didn't know her and I haven't, yeah, and I said no.
And she kept insisting and she was doing coke one time and out of her mind
And and I just got sick of her though and she gave me her number all I still have her number
Gia said she lived in New Jersey and Gia was freaked out that she was begging her come stay with her
Because she always wanted to leave her parents house because she could do her own thing
But yeah, she chicken cakes is a sicko. I was the one done with her and blocked her because I told everybody I showed our communication everything
and now she's lying saying that I sent her
UPS boxes and all this shit
That's what Victoria would do for for another streamer. She sent him to oceans. She she did that because she did it through her
Boyfriend of John somebody
because they were talking about how they did it, that he said you could go to the post office,
or that's what he would do. But I didn't send her anything because I don't know her information.
She was just desperately trying to hit me up even in
Ski's chat and he blocked her he kicked her out because nobody liked her so she's insane and she's drunk and she's going at
Alex you you saw her because you told me she was on
And she's saying Alex is the biggest flip-flopper and she's sick of her and all that who what about her?
She's a flip-flopper
Because she was friends with somebody I was getting into it with and all of a sudden here
She is begging me to talk and everybody got sick of her and and beta and others were even saying you know
Yeah, I was they were agreeing with what I said that she had complained about her
She thought she was creepy and a druggy. Oh
And so I was done with her and I got rid of her it's like who the fuck is she you know
Did they see the DX kicked her out because she wanted money over food being sent to her
And so she was desperate and tell me she'd coke and do I want to do coke and I mean she it was just weird
And I barely knew her and she was creepy
So I have all that from the path and she gave me the number
No DX gamble DX a group. Okay. Oh, yeah. Okay. Well, you know
Alan's is starting a live right now
It says open panel for all at the suggestion of Q45
Brandon dox my location
Exclamation point question mark. What is your location? Yeah, she's saying Q45 or Brandon or she's saying Brandon dox my location
She's saying it's the name of the live
Oh, really? I don't know. I've been pretty much gone. I did go into his chat for a little bit.
I think I mentioned chicken cakes. There was no mention of Alex.
But that bitch is saying Alex is a flip-flopper so many are have been flip-flopping, but she's worse
And she was kicked out of every community
Thanks to KK who got sick with of her
And everybody else kicked her out and she was gone and she can't live without the internet because her her husband
I guess he's crippled or something
They don't speak together. He sees somebody else
Yeah, you know and then she even had her little boy when he was small
Writing with lipstick or whatever and on her breasts and people remember that she needs to be gone
Oh my god, that's he needs to be gone. It'll be the shining though. Is he going red?
I know, right? Yeah, it's time that she'd be gone and a lot of people agree because I was in a chat a minute ago
somebody pulled me in about her and
Yeah, they're looking to get rid of her not not not physical not not like life
Off the internet because
Brandon said oh I have proof that
Karen said she was gonna kill Crystal. Did you see that? No, he was mad. Yeah, he was mad. There's no proof for that
I never said that I'm not talking about killing people. No because it's in text. No
Yeah, we talked yesterday. He was just upset that I was on your panel and
He's got sensitive though psyche and
Um, you know, I guess he's he was hurt. I don't know what happened when he was on panel with you
But yeah, he just holds on to it
Of my panel for right now because he came up call me pedophile today
Instead I had a kid as a moderator
He kept yelling it and saying so he said today's day one
It's gonna get worse for me every day and stuff and so he's just like threatening me
And so I think I'm just gonna keep my distance, but it's fine. It's like
You know you I mean you can have your own relationship
I just don't want to like interfere with your relationship. Yeah, I'm careful with everybody because that was wrong to say that because
Crystal is paranoid and she probably could run with it and say oh, yeah
This happened because she always plays victim and that's why her friend there
You know the one that she called all the time for help is completely done with her and she doesn't appreciate her
Telling Ella that she's fake because everybody's seen her on panel. She never used filters
She's very pretty and so that's why I posted that's that video on top about Jamie
Yeah, cuz Ella put on there in and then it's Ella that uses all these filters. They call her filter queen
Yeah, and I showed her her real picture that somebody sent so yeah, how dare her go at Jamie
She's just hurt because like her ex friend said
Kayla who I talked to
Um, she said when she ended the friendship with Ella a long time ago, it was over $600
and Ella didn't care.
So she blocked Ella everywhere and she was tired of her plain victim about this person
did this to me or my ex abused me.
But then there she was saying, I love you to that ex, um, I think Facebook or some other
platform that they saw.
But yeah, so then her and she would have Jamie on panel against me and Crystal
So Jamie got fed up with her and she was the one that helped me with the court thing because she was a witness and she's wrote them a long
email and I couldn't believe it so a
King and all of them got involved and showed how Ella was trying to hit me up in Rick's chat
Because if she put that charge on me, why was she like trying to talk started talking to me saying my name?
And talking about Carissa, and it was like are you how dare you after what you did would try to you know
Put me through the court thing, but it was deferred and and gone in three months
You know and I never got in trouble in 1982. I was in school. I didn't have any trouble at all
It's crazy. I was in Utah. I never got I never I never got in any trouble anywhere else
It was not until
Houston and I was like
No, yeah, no 25 and it was just turned 86 or whatever
But yeah, I did probation and they dropped the drugs that they found at my place
But yeah, I did that probation and that was
It and yeah, that was and then this time in 2023 because of Ella and that was deferred
But other than that I nothing I mean tickets traffic tickets. Yes. I got but you know, it's just ridiculous to lie
Like the image I made of you and think that is I don't look like that blonde hair and
Well, I know you don't like that with the Texas bikini though. Hey, is it okay? So that crystal and a thumbnail
Oh, they're asking about this picture. I put in the thumbnail. No, this is like, you know
I don't know I don't like to pose pictures of kids
But this is actually SIG's baby photo and he looks so cute in his baby photo. I mean here
This is just six. That's him in his baby photo. That looks like crystal
Because the blowfish
Let me do a screenshot. Yeah, cuz she's over there trying to make a having people do a a's of
yeah eyes of people and then she freaks out when they do it back to her get that one
yeah and crystal lost jamie who was the one that tried to help her and be on the phone with her
till she'd go to sleep and because she felt bad for her and she thought she changed but then look
at her she's calling jamie out with her op barb and jamie doesn't owe her three hundred dollars and
That Bob finally admitted that no, no, she doesn't so why lie for for a couple of years?
It's just some of these people are crazy though
And I'm sick of it. It's just so but you don't so today
I pretty much stayed off and stayed busy and and stuff and then you told me about the what was going on
On the performance panel with the chicken cakes and you could tell she's drunk and high and she's miserable because her man
Is with another woman right now
Oh my gosh, I mean I heard him I mean he sounds like he's like, you know half alive
I mean he's like half alive. Yeah, the tea was crippled or something. Yeah
Yeah, he's always like fuck you like yeah, he needs to be gone for good
She's obsessed with that. She has a cat litter box right next to her bed
Was it which is nasty? I mean, you know, she's she's a piece of shit with no life and she's miserable
She was going at Alex
because she's drunk and high and miserable, you know, if anybody's gonna be right, you know,
I mean, I think I'll go at her now because I've never sent her anything. I never knew her address.
And I'll go ahead and show Gia's communication with all of us about her that she was cringe and
begging her to come stay with her in New Jersey. That's all I know that she's in New Jersey.
And, you know, that her husband would take off and be with another woman.
And he was already getting sick and stuff, but he's hardly there with her and remember that she had her her little boy
And he was little
Draw all over her boobs with with I don't know if it was lipstick or what but that's nasty. She needs to be gone
I mean, you know, and then she said I'd called CPS on people
I never called CPS because I definitely would have called on her
Yeah
But yeah, what do you think of her? She's a nutcase so what she's going on Alex is like who the fuck do you think you are bitch you coke head
You could tell she was on coke
I used to do coke and plus she's drinking and that's why she went off at Alex because she's an ass-kisser
Towards everybody the way she'd call me wanted money. I didn't give her shit because I didn't like her and I knew she was shady
Well, yeah, I know I mean chicken can't I just see if she's like, you know good times really likes her boobs
He's really into her like breasts and stuff
And then she does these streams where she kind of like just shows almost her whole breasts and they're big
But it's like they're almost too big, you know, yeah too big. She's fat. She's nasty looking
I mean like that time when Alex went at her on that live and she was upset and she was fucked up and
Her head. No, it was a recap and alive that she was on and her head was dropping. She was definitely doing coke
And she does she does meth sometimes. Did you see her face?
Oh, who does meth? Um chicken cakes. Oh my god
Yeah, she was like going nuts about Brandon and stuff. Yeah, and then me again
It's like bitch. You're the one that was up my ass asking for money and help and oh
I can you can do this and get in stream yards and help you and it was like I didn't even know her
I just saw that she was a nasty bitch that everybody kicked out of even the Carter verse. They couldn't stand her
I still talk to Melanie
Where's that name from chicken cakes like what because what kind of oh the Christian was obsessed with chicken Andy
He's probably young enough to be his her her son
and
Who's going to alex at saman panel tonight somebody said in the chat?
Yes on that who does she think she is?
well, I mean she's also at um, you know, she was a good times last night with q 45 and it says
Oh positive panel and they were just talking about 80s music and stuff, but I mean
I don't know if she was in, she was in Bita's chat and then she's over at Sam-Ans and, you
know, she's doing her rounds.
I mean, it's just like-
Yeah, she doesn't have a live period, you know, and she had said how Alex is always
on Blive247.
No, I don't see anybody on there as much as her jumping on all these panels, giving
her sob story, crying, but Good Times made her cry and she made a live where she's crying
that he hurt her, kind of like she was in love with him or something.
Yeah, well, I mean, she's always the Tommy James now she wants to do a scap in her with Tommy James and Skelly and you know
Her that's why we always laughed when I used to follow the owls
They made fun of her and they'd kick her out. He couldn't stand her. Nobody likes this bitch
Kk still won't talk to her. She was done with her and like a cry baby
She was crying and she was gone for quite some time because nobody wanted her around
Well, I mean I say well because it's like she because of when she changes her personality so much and it's so yeah
And she's fucked up today going at Alex the what the fuck she's a druggy of the worst kind meth and coke
Okay, cuz she told me about cut math before and it was somebody else that we know that was on that call with us because
Oh, I had a gathering trust her so that connected them
And she was saying that you know meth is cheaper or something and she was struggling and she wanted money
Could I help her out and I said fuck? No, you know, it's like who do you think you are?
I don't need help with my stream yards. I don't intend on going live
So and she kept hitting me up every day
Well, I guess I don't have her number. This is backstage. Who?
His initials are bq. I don't know who that is
You don't know anybody with those initials. No, it's probably a fake account. No, it's somebody you know with initials bq
I don't know any bq
This is initials. It's Brandon. Oh, yeah, let him up. You let him up. Okay, so Brandon
Changing his name though. You can't have that name. I have to change your name or I'll change it for you
Oh, she was bashing him too. She just now she was bashing Brandon
And he didn't even do anything to her. She was hitting them up.
She hits everybody up.
See, that's his cat. It's the Siamese cat. He is good with that cat. He loves that cat.
See? So there's no abuse there because a cat wouldn't be like that all loving up on, you know, him if they were freaked, you know.
Cuz I've seen cats that are abused and you know, they don't want have anything to do with whoever's there
See and look how healthy that cat looks. It's a beautiful cat
Cats happy very happy. I'm serious and he adores that cat
Yeah, that is a beautiful cat. Look how good he takes care
He's had the cat now for a while because Crystal was saying how he stole that from somebody
No, that's his cat and his cat looks healthier and happier than her cat
Who was declawed?
Yes, you got his legs off. Yeah, she kept the toes up pretty much
I saw that because somebody cuz I'm gonna go crazy. Look at them. Okay. They look
Look at the bullshit ass nigga
What's up, bitch
Fuck my dick you bitch ass nigga. I'm out of here PDF ass nigga and I am next to the portrait
Oh, fuck you miss Fang miss tango. We're very afraid
Stang
Yeah, you are a PDF. You like little kids. Yeah, that's what I like little boys. Can't get him off
You know, he's a bitch he's a bitch you
Yeah, look at
Hey, what's up, Samman? Hey, what's up, Samman? Hey, what's up?
Bro, you know I used to beat a bro. You know I went to your city and I beat up people in your city
Yeah, he's a weirdo
He's a man. He was he runs from Barry. He probably avoided their live the other day
Yeah, I know and he's on every day. They said like 24 seven and somebody I will know I think that there's one person though Brandon and they're pretty much stalking him and recording everything he does but then why is he on as much as him.
He did a chronicle of salmon come me come back on tell me come back on back to come back on bitch
Yeah, come back on bitch left on his own. I didn't kick him off. Yeah. No, see he's a coward
And he's terrified of guys
Come here me so
Come here. I got one. I'm gonna make a name. He flies in the air. He jumps by the ceiling. Come here. Oh, wow
Come at me. So yeah, he's fucking crazy. Yeah
Look at him. There he is. Yeah
He's so cute. Yeah, he's so cute. Look, he's happy
Link directly to my family hotel Albuquerque, what's what's that at Old Town? She's in Albuquerque
right now
But hey, if you want to go to hotel Albuquerque, I encourage you to they could probably use the business
Make sure you either get a room or a bar or a restaurant.
Something along the line.
She needs to visit Santa Fe.
Judge is not gonna look favorably upon that
Y'all see the live stream go live stream over there in Albuquerque
I don't remember that hotel. I've never had a thing. Nothing was there when you lived in oh, I'm gonna send you a picture dude
Send you a picture of Albuquerque when you live here. There was nothing here. I'm gonna send you a picture of
When did you live here in the 60s and the 70s? No, it was late 70s late late 70s. Yeah, it was when I was in
High school
I'm going to send you a picture. There was nothing here. There's nothing out here. Where do you live here?
I I graduated in 29
We're out with good kids. I went to the academy and a private school like yeah
But I was my lead and my parents got mad and then they put me in sandia high school
There was nothing out there back then. I have a picture of back then and back then out there. There was nothing out there
Yeah, that's what I'm saying
We go to the tram to get classes and go to the tram and and go up on the mountain
Yeah, basically back then in the city. Nothing was out here back then and now it's a big-ass city
Difference yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm gonna send you I'm gonna send you pictures back
And the pictures now and you saw my parents house our house. You said yeah
Back then yeah back then was only that school in a few houses in their big-ass houses the house that you live in
It was full.
It was a big neighborhood.
Yeah.
It was a whole thing.
But that was new.
That was new.
That was from the 70s.
In the 60s, there was nothing.
Ten years before that, there was nothing.
I was there in the 60s.
Yeah.
I was there.
That's what I'm saying.
I was there in 76.
Those houses were new.
Yeah.
When you look there, those houses were new.
The houses were there.
Those in the 70s.
Yeah.
But outside of the Pelletsverdes, we'd live in an academy of states.
Pelletsverdes.
I'm sorry.
Um, San Mateo remember there now there was yeah, there was yeah, there was nothing there now
But now it's full of now. Let's see now. There's all kinds of shit there
Much over there is
Ice cream plays, but there wasn't that much there. I heard there's a lot of shit. Yeah
My brother was just there now, but kirkie he goes there
He went to pick up a show quality pecanese that they have now we went and bothered over there
Yeah, there's a show of the houses
Yeah, I can imagine because that's what he said, you know, but he went to our house and he doesn't like that
They took the pull out
and they put a
Cool that you are to take care of they all got rid of one bro because
They just grow out he did nobody swimming in them. They don't have kids
All the kids. Yeah, that's that's weird that they take a pull-up because everybody has
What it is is everybody had a pool, but what happened is everybody's kids grew up and they don't go home
That much, you know, I mean, yeah, yeah, Alex should go check it out where we lived. It was and you know charger trail
in Academy of States
You know, so yeah, there's some famous yeah, that's cool. Yeah, I know a lot of people that went to that school, dude
A lot of people I went to the school. No
Academy a lot of people went to the military that were in that school
My brother went to boom Mexico Military Institute in Roswell. Oh, yeah. Oh, I was gonna go to that dude
I was my dad was gonna put me in it, but they said that since I didn't consent to it
They could they weren't gonna put me in it. They asked me do you know that?
my dad was gonna put me in that nimi it's called nimi yeah it's in roswell dude it's a military school
yeah roswell that's what i saw they asked me they asked me dude yeah when i went there the
they asked me they were like do you consent to this and i said no and they're like he's not
allowed to join he's not allowed to join oh my god yeah i was like i was like yeah i was like yeah i was
like they're like do you consent to this i was like honestly i don't want to go here bro i just
Because that's all I did. I was like, I just want to play my video games, dude. You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, and my dad tried to put me in that school dude
I was like fuck no dude, and they're like do you consent? I was like, no, dude. I don't consent
I was like, I just want to keep playing my video. But that's what happened, dude
I used to get drunk dude the same thing that I'm doing now I used to do when I was a kid
I would get drunk. I would get drunk as fuck dude and I'll play Counter-Strike source
Yeah
Damn, yeah, the weather was perfect there except for the winner. It was icy
Now it's warm. It's not even that hot they're saying that it's hot in front
They're saying that it's hot in France and hot in New York and shit. It's not that hot over here. I could yeah, I could
It's not no matter what every evening it'd be nice and cool. That's what I do no matter how hot it'd be in the summer time
Every evening it'd be nice and that's what I'm saying. It's not that hot over here
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. It's not that hot here now everybody
And and then we came to hell which is Houston and not that this night is just
It's a swamp. I hate it. The heat. It's like, damn. I hate that. That's a hot place. So Texas
Even the part of Texas that's by the border, that's drier. That's less hot, dude.
Right. San Antonio is nice. It reminded me of the Albuquerque weather when we went over there
And that's still humid. That's more humid than here.
Feel a little bit in there. Yeah, but compared to Houston, it was nice. And uh, yeah.
Houston, that's it. That's one of the
Think about it. That's one of the most southern cities
Yeah, man, Florida is more southern but Florida. That's what that fucking for that
speaking of Florida
That bad boy breeze I do the fucking weirdo, dude
I'm sorry, baby. You're just aware though. Yeah, it's like you get on psyche get on care
Get on fucking stream you bitch ass nigga
He leaves like a little bitch get on stream he says that get on stream you fuck that's fucking pussy
Get on streamer. I'm leaving dude. I'm leaving your shame if you don't get on
The chat
He's lying you see how he's playing those sounds
No, he's what are you doing bro get on the fucking stream bitch. I don't have to say about chicken cakes you guys especially you know
She's been DMing me. She's been DMing me on Instagram. Oh, yeah, that's what she does. He's a weirdo
Yeah, and I know he's high and the coke head and and Matt wants me to fuck her. She was DMing me on Instagram
She wants me to fuck her
Yeah, chicken kegs. Are you serious? Yeah, like he's fucked up remind sometimes
Even
You know Lindsay Lindsay wants me to smash it right
Yeah, I don't know her too well Lindsay, but that chicken case she needs to go man. That's video. That's that video is funny though
Huh gamble saying them. What does he say that he wants a dick or boyfriend dick pics?
Yeah, I
Did I went ahead and share that psyche you watch it because yeah, that's
I saw that dick
Lindsay said it Lindsay said it that he asked her for
Big pic and and she only gave it to him and I clicked it you ought to watch it. I have it in my short story
Anybody wants to send me a dick pic, you know, you can go to my disc. Fuck you. Don't start talking gay
Bro because you're taking me off your you too much disrespect bro, I'm a human being taking me off panel kicking me off
Saying oh look at my dick. Look at my ass. Treat me like a fucking human being motherfucker. Look at my dick
Bro, no, you're showing you were showing your ass and your speed. I was saying look look and then kicking me off panel and shit
Treat me like a human being dog. Yes. You said it was you said I was disgusting
No, that was me. No, I was saying you're disgusting because you were doing that. Yeah, don't try to say that I know
So don't do it then
I like to do it
Then you're gay, bro
Discussing
Discuss
Yeah, don't show me your dick. You're trying to show me his dick in shit
You say you spread your ass, but not your asshole, I don't know the difference
Like Sam and then he spread his own gamble
Gamble tries to say that I showed his ass, bro that dude spread his asshole for a little kid dog
Yeah, I saw that little last other video too. Yeah, he spread his ass for a little-ass kid
Well, didn't you go gamble your butthole?
That's a grown man.
He showed his ass to a little kid.
I know.
I'm not blaming you.
I think it was a chance down to that.
I'm still looking for that clip.
He is sick, dude.
Why do you want to see my asshole, dude?
He is sick, motherfucker.
I think Brandon has the clip.
He shows the video.
You see?
Oh my gosh.
Did he send it to me, Brandon?
Yeah
Why do you delete that minor that you had on here? Oh, yeah, I forgot bro that there's a minor in this chat, dude
That's a kid, dude, I told you that
No, no, that's just how YouTube is sometimes a little kid will join your shit
Yeah, didn't they try to join Kate, but she didn't let him up. Yeah, there was it. I think that's the same. You're right
That's the same little kid. That's I guarantee you that's just you know that right last time
I think that chicken kick son
No, it's not it. No, it's a little girl. Oh, it is. They joined Kate Street. It's a little girl
They joined a stream and they like they're like they're like who they're like who is this and then it was literally bros a little girl talking
Yeah
That's the same person that's in you it just happens dude they join this shit
No
There's a video of Gamble showing his ass when he's seeing Gamble showing his ass
Do you want to fuck his ass when you see that?
There's a video of him showing his ass
On the video of Gamble showing his ass. Do you want to fuck him?
Yeah, on the video of Gamble showing his ass
You know, there's a video of him showing his ass to a little kid, right?
I see it
But I can't show that you didn't your channel get taken down for showing that so I can't show that video
I put it up and they go I well it must not be because I put it up in the algorithm algorithm gave it 2,000 views
But then it was like, you know considered like some kind of endangering
I put it back I put it why I uploaded again on this channel and it got 2,000 views instantly
I don't know, it's hard for me to hate people or get mad at people, it's like I really don't respect my own shit.
Do you see how I always say that she's an Albuquerque? Do you see how I prove that she's an Albuquerque?
Yeah.
But she was outside, so think about it. That's how somebody could doxy, you know that, right? If you're sitting outside...
And you let the sun go down and you show look this is when the sun went down. They got dark. You know that doctors you right?
You know that doctor you right?
She was an Albuquerque, so yeah, no, no, no, she's saying that she's in Arizona
She's saying that she's in Arizona. Oh
She was sitting outside on Sam Man's panel and it went black and I looked and it went why I said look at look
I said lucky what a coincidence. I look outside and it was picked by the minute that it went nighttime
It went nighttime on a string
Arizona Scottsdale an hour before that the Sun is still up dude
The Sun was set to go down and get dark the Sun was still up in Arizona
So that's how she would expose.
So basically she's saying she's in Arizona.
But she's outside live streaming. Yeah on Samman's panel and they got dark at the exact same time
They got dark here in Albuquerque. So that's how you know. She's in Albuquerque
Well, they said something about fruit street somebody asked me. Do you know what fruit? I didn't know
Yeah, she's here
She was at like on a video on fruit street like walking through
Good street, okay, that's fucking us there. Yeah, I guess I don't know. I don't think she's in the hotel
Though I think she's in there B&B. That's where she stays
Okay
It's because she works for Amazon. She gets like a deal on like air being these or something. Oh, I want to say
Okay, clumsy. I'm so sorry because I thought okay. Tell me get on tell me to get on with this red ball
I'm gonna get on with the red ball
Yeah, that's him. Yeah, he's a full-time male escort
Yeah, he's lying if he said it
I've done the real video. This is what this is what that actually happens in the video. Look at this
Psyche look at it. Oh, he was blowing a balloon
Psyche look at his look at his YouTube profile dude. He has a picture of a little kid holding a pistol
Look at his profile picture. No, no look at his profile picture now on his YouTube. It's a picture of like a little
13 14-year-old little boy holding up a pistol like that to the camera. Is that your son or what is that your son?
Or who is that? Who's that little kid?
He has a picture of a little like a little kid holding up a gun like that to the camera dude a little fucking kid
Look at his profile picture on his YouTube. Yeah, the red ball. What is that that red ball? That was a balloon
It was supposed to be that's when you got that's when he got raped in prison
They were taking pictures of him that he got raped in prison
That's how big his butthole got right there
It's not showing it's not showing it's not showing
This was the original though
Open your screen. It's not showing I
Well, I don't that mean I think I don't know if it's showing on yours, but yeah, yeah, that was clumsy and I don't know
I don't know he's saying he's saying a red ball and his face is I don't know if it's a red face or something
It looks like he is an emoji. That's right. He has a red ball
He's a red ball. What do you use that ball clumsy? Is that like something you put you put it in that in your butt?
It's a ball gag. It's to shut him up from the guards hearing him when he's getting fucked in the ass
It's from the guards hearing when he's getting ass fucked and they don't hear that he shuts his fucking mouth
Guys, I would like sponsor like a red ball for like a gag ball for like Sam and you just like I bet yeah
Yeah, Sam I need one Sam and Polly has one
Hey, he probably has a goal. I didn't his brother
He's got a background where he he tied some a guy up a kid a young somebody real young and
Grape to him
That's right. It's not worth it because
You're right Karen. It's not worth it because these live streams that we do this nice gamble man and all my enemies
You're right. It's not worth it. You might as well make a man. Do you know what I mean?
It makes them happy if we get mad at each other.
You know, I think oh, yeah, because I saw resonance say that and she's a big snake
Yeah, I mean me out of money and she went ahead and paid me back later after she stood me over
She called me one day and she said I'm at the store and I'm short and my husband forgot to get of the buns or bread
Shit not me and I told her then just why don't you go through your change? I'm sure you got enough change
and then she was loudly counting her chain at 50 cents at 60 70 80 and then she went to the dollar
and then 139 and she goes oh i got it yeah bitch you scamming bitch did you see her face yeah
she's going to money to gamble that's the only last person that's a money gamble because when she
Um, she was said that she took a lot of secret information out of their mug chest that they had in there
And I'm gonna screw him over
That's the same thing I did with cats. That's like the same shit. I did that's not like the same shit
I wear cats the Australian method game developer
There's an Australian mess had game developer that was gambles top-modern. I flipped him against him
And then she went over there crawling up to enemies asked to join his group for the one that
You know his son I guess got sick or whatever him. Yeah
Yeah, and now she's donating to
Yeah, yeah, so her post she has a nerve to post on my page saying I like to watch
Karen and Brandon fight or something like that is with a fuck
You know, I went ahead and hit her for my channel. It's like who the fuck are you and
So yeah, she was attacking my friend
Jamie I'll show you
Resonance picture
Look at he goes. He jumps in the air. He fucking jumps in the air for the toy. See how cute
Goes crazy. Let's see if he he sometimes he doesn't do it. Sometimes he goes crazy for it
And you don't even gotta get in there for him. I don't think he's gonna go crazy. But yeah, he's not
Yeah, he's not
With those I got a laser too for them. Yeah, he's not in them sometimes he'll jump he goes fucking nuts dude
He fucking
He fucking jumps crazy and I put it in the air and he jumps in the air dude
He jumps like three or four feet in the air and correct to grab the joy, especially with those
It's like the youngest one does that especially she'll be pulling up in the air trying to catch
It's a little little birds or whatever on the end and he's already getting old
He's already like six years old seven years old. Really? Yeah
Yeah, they did live up to 18. I don't know mine mine was the he's from the city
He's from he's from new york city, dude
He's a little look look at them dude. I'm gonna show them
Look at them
Let's get a little kid. Yeah, it's so cute me so he's about see it look how happy
He's like a weasel though, dude. I told you dude. Yeah, I told you if you seen the weasels
Have you seen the weasels? He's like, yeah, look at his body. It's like a long
It's like a weasel dude. He has like a weasel body
It's like having a pretty yeah, they perfect people say I have the body of a weasel sometimes
Oh, no, there was this kid. I was in jail with his name was we though that was his game name
His head. He was like a little fucking weasel, dude
They have a long body look at his long. He has like a tube body. It's like a long toothpaste tube like a tube
Uncomfortable
Let's see if he goes crazy with this. No, he's not him. He's when he's in the mood to be pet when he's in the mood
He doesn't play with a toy when he's in the world and he just loves to be loved by his dad
Yeah
He goes crazy with that toy though sometimes with the toys. They'll jump he jumps in the air
He just he jumps like fucking like six feet in the like five feet in the air dude and grabs it
My youngest one does that too, especially jumps up in the air. The others don't are okay
They'll play a little bit, but yeah that one she loves the toys and the little plastic toys
She'll toss them all in the tub
and she'll go in there just bouncing on them like she's a hockey player or something.
It'll get noisy in the morning because that's when she does it. She'll take each each plastic ball in there like four, like five or four.
And then y'all can hear her pouncing on them and I go look and there she is pouncing
And she always puts it in the tub because because she likes it like that with the pounce on it and they bounce back
To her it's like yeah, she has a ball every morning with those with those little balls. So I ordered more for her
Yeah, I love the little toys. I got a lot of toys. I got I ordered another tunnel
Um, yeah, new clippers. Um, they already have plenty of food and just a lot of toys and uh
I don't know other things that they'd like so you know like another tunnel because there's four of them now
Yeah, yeah, but they're happy cats, but she's the most playful
And one neighbor was shocked. They said, oh my God, I've never seen that, you know
I was outside and she said look look at your window upstairs and I looked and I see my
Peek-a-nees and he has to the cats side by you know next to him one on the right one on the left
And they look like buddies and they were like looking at me and following follow
You know watching me like where's our mommy come back?
And the neighbors were laughing and they said how adorable look of them and I look up and I see them
They're just looking at me like come home mommy
All three of them
So they get along great
There's so many cats that's all on facebook. They're posting that there's all kinds of um
Kids that people need to pick up and take care of they said they're all infected and sure
Yeah, that's crazy, huh man. Yeah
I should go get them and fucking
I don't know what should I what would you do in that case?
What with the Spiral cats?
Yeah, they said that on the street that I live on dude. There's all kinds of cats doing kittens you and they're all fucked up
dude
They have eye infections and all that dude, and there's like
Yeah
Well, that's the organization the organization is the one that said that they said they're too full
Yeah, and they said that they need help with the street that I live on. No, no all of them
No, they do they do the rescues are saying that they're too full that they have their hands
Oh with all kinds of shit and that the street that I live on there's all kinds of kittens
Yeah, they have like
That's like that dog. Oh, I was at the gas station a day and I saw a tweaker dude and he had a dog and it was like
It was a fucking
It was the English Bulldog, but it's eyes were all infected
From the heat cuz it's hot. Yeah, he stole it. I know that fucker stole it
Oh my god, and it was harder than and it was harder than it's harder than fuck
You could tell the dog is dying from the heat it wanted that you could tell it wanted hold the stealing can't yeah
I feel yeah, that's what I thought. I felt like fucking still in the fucking dog
From the motherfucker dude
Cuz I had seen this guy
He was homeless and and his poor dog was suffering in the heat or whatever
And I saw the guy and I went to see the dog and pet him and I sat next to him and I said look
I said, you know, I said are you you need help with this dog and?
he said oh some lady just gave it to me and i said well do you mind because i probably have
somebody that'll take good care of it you know because the dog you know looked weak it was a
pug and so i gave him some money and i took the dog and i found him a good home and that person
still posts that dog on facebook and he's happy with their their other dog
And then in the yard, so I'm glad he's doing good, but yeah, he was like struggling and that guy just didn't seem to care
He was homeless and
Yeah, he was just sitting on a bench and yeah, I'm glad I took that doctor. You might ask him and see
You know you could probably help a dog
Yeah, it's great. It's great to do things like you know
Actually, like you know good things in the world too because it's like those the good things you come back to you
It's like me. Oh, we have another guest on one second
Or I love the brand and drop off. Are you ever in the whole thing?
I'll brand is probably yeah, I dropped off. Okay. Here he is. Hey, my my
Thank you, he's frozen there. Oh, yeah, he froze
There I call you littles and you're the bullying cat
The bully cats here with me she's snuggling to me like don't want attention just by myself because she's
She's a bully that the other
She doesn't like to share me
You know I love a good I love a good
Cute cat video and there's actually this channel called the Dodo. Have you heard of the Dodo?
Oh, that's a rescue. I think I just I yeah the dodo. I always see their clips on IG
You could call a different rescue because I've rescued cats though, too
That way, you know, these kids were painting a cat red and I called her a rescue person
I found and she came in and got the cat. Can you please save Abby?
Oh, what should I do all those cats that they said are on my street?
Yeah, what should you do about it? Like I would say, you know, like well, you know, it's like it's hard feed them
Just feed them if you can feed them
But then it's like reproducing something like that. I would say like take it like say taking some. Oh, yeah
That's what they're saying. They're saying they want people to trap them. They're like, oh, we need trappers over here
We call them trappers
They used to do that here until COVID where they once a year because there was a lot of
cats and and they would trap them and take them because they'd tell us keep your pets inside.
There's a big ass fucking um ragdoll signees dude it's like a ragdoll.
Are you serious there? Yeah it's like fluffy yeah it runs around it comes to my door dude
and it's like fluffy dude it's like a signees cat but it's fluffy.
Like long hair. Yeah
Yeah, I bathe my cats. Do you bathe your cats?
Psyche you don't need it this
But yeah, they don't need it they clean themselves so good, but still yeah
I don't bathe them all the time and like every every three months or so and yeah
Yeah, this cat he's found the grains
I'm like, it's not like rain dude. I don't even need to wash him or nothing dude. He always smells like
Yeah, that's a beautiful cat me. So it's his name. That's a cute name
Boys that still needs a name, but you know, I'm sharing him with the neighbor. Oh
Yeah, but another baby
When I was a little kid that's what I used to do used to catch cats
So I might start just cashing all those cats well when I drive down the street
I see nice looking cats
Really? Yeah, God we had a problem here, but a lot of neighbors helped us and you know helped
catch them and
We vetted them and they helped find homes for them
To all of us did so a bunch of we don't have a cap problem as much as we did before
Yeah
That's what they said that they said just that they need someone to go out there and catch them and turn them all in they said
Yeah, they don't they don't
They fix some fix some and they clip their ear and they put them back out there
Oh really if you put them back out there yeah but at least yeah they're fixed and they clip
their area and they feed them. Yeah because I've seen some with clipped ears before and that was
them they that's when they would catch them and and fix them and then release them back
but now they're not even doing that anymore since COVID down here you know it's like we're all on
our own. They started doing it again out here they do it out here.
Yeah, so I need to just catch all those cats out there and just turn them in to them
Yeah, the baby cat kind of looks like my my cat that passed away at 20 and
I didn't know because the manager said I went over there to the office to talk to them about the something and
I saw that baby cat there the mother I saw the mother rejecting her because I go we feed the feral
And I remember the mother and that baby would eat together no matter what but then she started like rejecting him like you know
He's still little and I thought in front of the office with a bowl of water and I said
Yeah, now he's there night and day and they said they you know, they feed them and water or whatever and I said is it okay for me to
Get no, it's a she and they said it's a female and they said is it okay if I
I take her and I say well good luck because everybody's caught her and and she keeps running back here
Well, then the only way they can run back there is if you let him out the door. I mean they don't open doors
So I'm gonna try because she was used to me feeding him or she I keep the sheet with feeding her
It's a female and she'll follow me sometimes, but yeah, I just
I'm gonna try that's why I got a towel and everything because now I know that that's where she is at night
So because when I see the other feral, I'll see him come out
But he seems to come afraid to join the cast because the mother would hiss at him and
You know, I've sent you I guess she was just trying to let him know that he's on his own now that he's not a baby
But he's still small
So I'll see how that goes. I'll see if I can get him. I'll take a towel out there and food and then just put him in a towel and run home
Before I get scratched
But it's a sweet cat and I see it all by itself over there in front of the office and you know
But he was she was happy with her mom with the other cat. She won't even join the other feral cat
She's all by herself now
But yeah, I think I'm gonna do that tonight though go over there and just pick towel and give her food and
Bring her in
I mean get her fixed. So I gotta get that prepared
You know, you know
I'm gonna start doing that. I'm gonna start catching all those calves outside. But yeah, if you can yes
But you also look up places you'll be surprised and the computer Google places
That's how I found some rescues that are far away and they've helped sometimes still
Because the main rescue person she was back into abusing a prescription drugs
It's learning her words and not doing what she's supposed to though
I had to call other places if we needed really some help and
They've shown up
Well, yeah, it just kind of sucks though
Yeah, there's a lot of cats out here on my street. Mm-hmm
See and there were a bunch of them here, you know, and they thank me for you know
Helping with a problem because they said on one side of the property was full of them
I remember there were but now they're you know, we
Put him in crates, and I got a lot of neighbors to help and and the rescue person came in and took him
Yeah, look at to the shelter that she runs which is in Katie and
You know so I'm glad so we did get rid of the problem most of the problem
But yeah, that's that where did psyche go now? I thought he was gonna say something about what happened
psyche
You know Q Q 45 killed his cats, you know that right? Oh, no, I don't want to think that no he didn't kill those
No, no, he showed his cats and look all dead
Cuz I keep seeing that he's showing the cats and he's yeah, but
I don't know
Dumped all of us
One's for no reason like really if she was mad at Brandon, but now she says I'm gonna I'm in it
She's crazy. She's she's an Albuquerque. She's fucking nuts. She came over here
She thought all they're gonna bone her and it was a weird timing that I that I said fuck you
You know that it was a weird timing bro right when she came here to Albuquerque
That was when that she happened with Sam and and I cut her off
Yeah, that's when you got mad because she was with she was already here. She's already here. She's ready for the day
Yeah, that's what I think yet cuz she's here dude. Why did she come to Albuquerque? I mean just for me because she wanted some day
Yeah, I don't fuck man
What if I get really if I'm really cute cuz doesn't he like them boys?
Is that salmon and Julio
Oh, like you let you got off cam and that's true even now Barry all of them know that the
The story that his I think clumsy said it first and if you look it up, it's true
The brother got in trouble because he did like great but a guy years ago
I don't know where it was that or whatever, but they were all discussing it and salmon
Actually, I got that didn't happen because when he tried to join that panel he disappeared because Barry Tommy
KK was there
And I forget who else and he's just scared of guys because look at how he disappeared when when Brandon went at him
He's terrified of guys
You know, he just like they said even KK said it he just tries to go out women
You're the pussy. Yeah, he is
How can he can't get on cam like I'm on cam?
Fucking bitch. I'm sure in my whole bedroom. So why are we talking about him anyway? I can't stand him
Oh, you know what somebody yeah
I do have the steps on how to do that cuz somebody did lose their channel
But then I got busy this week and when he goes up. I'm gonna go ahead and
Flip it and show them because that's what they need to
Clip it and and and all the channels that he's had and that way they'll see it
But you have to do the form just I'm gonna show you
Brandon and you'll see it's it's a lot of steps
But yeah, look how stupid he is out there in public still bullying people women and
That way it'll be taken down
But you have to give all his channels and that way they'll take down all those channels and proof that he's live on there
And you just clip it
Yeah, because I'd ever got freaked out. He's been around for a long time and and he's pissed that he can't even get on anymore
I don't know if he can use an IP different
But I think he can get in trouble for doing that
So that's why he's just bitching and pissed off because he's been a streamer for a lot of years and he had like four channels
No, Brandon. I don't know that lady is it looks like Linda trip. I don't I don't want to put up a picture of a woman
So just take that picture down
Here's a picture of some woman up. I know that's on him. So put a picture of the chicken cakes
He's the public druggy
It's supposed to go show chicken cakes
She was the one hitting me up and stuff for money and stuff
And now she's talking shit cuz I didn't like her nobody liked her and we made fun of her and Geo always complained about
pickles
Yeah, oh pickles are so cute
That's pickles
Yeah, yeah, he was on on a panel admitting that his podcast and the advertising and then he lies and that's not me
Yes, it is and Kiwi Farms is
Yeah, I don't have a video. I have a video. I have a video exposing him
And that woman that got scared of them Brandon, I forget she was a
Cardiverse yeah
No, no, we're in Katie. It's she had a nice popular name and I remember he had her on on
YouTube line saying she's a private detector and she was trying to change her voice
Everybody knew who she was
But then Kiwi Farms was looking for her and then she got paranoid
And a couple years later she disappeared when she was trying to get offline because they were out to get her and they found her on my IG because they found her and then all of a sudden they had all her pictures and information on her and she freaked out and then all of a sudden she told people, I think, because I don't think she really passed away but she was gone.
Yeah, I can and stuff. So, yeah, you know, he had a little kind of fucking prostitutes going to his little woods
who
Rg
Bitch, oh, really? Yeah. He's so weird again. They're looking for him. You were right
And you said that they do have a thread on Alex. What what does she do? Why are they looking?
Threatening to kill people with Donald Trump begging
Yeah, the one I was talking about she actually disappeared and somebody said it was serious, so I don't know what happened
I just thought well, that's so weird
Because I remember she was scared of them
and I'll
I'm sure he is yeah, I can't believe that we go he'll be live bro
He'll be live and he'll be live brown. I'll go I'll go to lunch break in the next day and he'll still be live
Yeah, I saw that one day, too
He turned he went live one night and then the next day
He was still live, and then he slept the rest of the day. I guess what kind of schedule is that he doesn't work
method method
Yeah, he doesn't work though
I remember he was on government assistance or whatever before but yeah, he's shady as fuck man
I've never known anybody so shady. He'll even lie for people like for crystal
Because he practically saw her as a celebrity or something and gamble like he's cracking on gamble
Yeah, I mean he's he's weird I mean and then he lied because words of proof about
be that telling him
Um, you know, what was it? He was upset about the beta. I
Don't know was it. It was something ridiculous and he lied about it
He just told a lot of lies and he got it. He got caught in in so many lies
Oh about about the miss some miscarriage. I think it was and
Show proof
He said that beta had a miscarriage or some shit
Don't know what it was something about a miscarriage, but it was a lot. No that that beta insulted him by because he said
He said he was vile and attacked his mom and so Alex said, you know
She wanted to see it and so when he he didn't do it because he was lying and and then all of a sudden two months later
He's mad at beta again
And then he said he had it names on his phone, but it's cracked but later he showed it and when I looked through that what he was showing
There was nothing there about any miscarriage. It was just him and me to talk and shit to each other
They were friendly at that time
And it's like well, where is the part where she did that to you because he said these are the tech of the DMs or whatever
He's a liar
Just like he was the other day calling somebody whispering. I'm gonna fuck you like a fuck my nephew
Was that to you too?
Yeah
You played it and somebody else got it too. He saw like a piece of shit. He did that. I mean damn
He's a pedophile, and he's not I mean he's got kids and a wife like and he's up all night like that
It's just isn't a wife. He has kids and wife, but yeah, he's a pedophile
Look at his profile picture now on his on his YouTube, it's a picture of a little boy holding a gun
Pointing the gun at the camera. I have a little boy. His wife though. She's huge
I'm gonna find out. I'm gonna find out who I'm gonna find out who that little boy is did
The little boy will get a fucking rape
Does that his son? I think I don't know who it is, but he has a picture of a little kid holding the gun
It's not a cartoon picture or anything like that. No, it's a little kid. Yeah. Yeah, it's a little kid holding the gun
The kids end up going to prison and getting raped just like you did fucking bitch
You got raped in prison that kids
Yeah, so did Samuel what they said I didn't see it, but they were talking about that. Oh my cats all up on me
Yeah, you came back. It's crazy. My cats calling on me
His parents are with him in spirit. Oh, it's so beautiful. I wish you guys could be here. Well
Maybe some of you, but I don't know about all of you
If all of you are here to be really fucked up. We're there now. We're there with you, metallo. We are there
I think I lost all the we got people's names. I don't understand
We're gonna be smoking some pocket. You've got that all fell into my pocket. You're a great one
Just get your degree get a certificate. I think we got some enough nuggets to get high off of oh, yeah
Oh, yeah
What's up Sharon we made it Sharon
Yeah
Well, you know what I'm I'm in the ocean
Streams like that beaches or you know out there
He never came to visit me and I wanted to be in speedos with him with with with with Q
Oh, I mean, he's cute ask him, did you tell him I told him he said he said he'd rather
be that he wouldn't he's the only the closest he's ever going to be to me is on the panel
with each other.
What happened to Brandon he fell out. Yeah, he said he was going to bed
Oh, you're going oh, thank you so much for being on the show. Yeah, yeah
Cuz I'm worried about that baby that I saw in front of the office
So I'm gonna take a towel with me and take food and nothing the barrels at nighttime, too
And I'm gonna see about bringing her here cuz they said that she runs back or he read she runs back over there
Okay, well wish me luck man. I hope she doesn't scratch me because they said that she doesn't stay wherever you know other people try to take her
So we'll see
Yeah, I love you too and and I have toys for her so she'll be happy. She's a baby
Okay, and then she looks like Lola too, she's uh, you know
Yeah, and looks like like my cat kitty who passed away at 20 in December
So okay, well good night. I'm gonna go ahead and do this now before it gets too late. Okay. Bye. Bye. All right. Bye
And an old yee who enter here
Tony's just full of it
Hunts chicken strud
Surround
Lookin' like a lunatic
Alexander
Welcome to the site
You're celled in the pan
Make it fry
The noise you're makin'
Can't hide inside
Welcome to the site
out of new york came a storm on wheels rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
cuban cigar lit like his temper pizza in one hand hot dog for dinner said psyche i'm bored had
to switch the scene left some poor woman screaming on live stream trolled her down to the void and
back then crashed my show like a heart attack gotty made man roll discord i miss italian mormon blend
They dangerous wild, but they still my friends
Yeah, love you God, until the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
sees god with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the
live feed bow to your king while smoking that leaf laughing at chaos like
it's comic relief brought spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones
they all jumped in cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the
wire but nah I like my circus I love this mess every trolls just a test stop
You're absurd and free, but deep down, you got loyalty
If your soul rolls like he's in control
Discord, the Amish should tell you more
They dangerous wild, but they still not
You got it till the bitter end, we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
you got layers like a deep dish slice under all that shade a heart made of ice and maybe rice
so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to psych you brought the
drama the heat for fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one got it crazy but your family now